Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
Yes, I am very happy to see you all here. So, good evening, everyone.
The morning chime has rung. We are Shirutei Art School.
Yay.
Yay!
We are the Sakura sisters.
This is the sakura sisters pose.
This pose is a combination of the hedge and the sunlight. I hope you will try it too.
So, before we start the show, I would like to choose today's MC.
Please vote for your favorite for the first place.
The person who has the number with that number written on it is today's MC.
Okay, everyone, let's start voting.
Let's start.
Good evening, Sakura Sisters. Not Sakura Sisters, Sakura Sisters.
Kombanmi.
We'll take that one, too?
Shall we pull it?
Or do you want me to pull it?
Which do you prefer?
I'll take this one.
Okay.
Please choose whichever you like.
Voting time. It's been a while.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Finished!
End, end.
Now, MC I'm good.
I'm doing Musashi training and stuff.
Yes, that's right.
So that's it,
Is it out?
55.4% for number 2.
44.6% for number 1
So, the number 2 is the one we usually have
Today's MC.
That's me!
It's me!
What, it's me.
Please be as usual.
I will do my best.
It's been a while since I've been in the showroom,
I will do my best with a lot of energy.
I look forward to working with you.
Once again, I will be today's MC.
My name is Kono Sakurai.
And my name is Mau Sakurai.
I look forward to working with you.
Let's get started.
Seino!
Ebichu's Delightful and Fufufu Showroom
Today is the 59th
Thank you very much for visiting our 59th showroom.
Thank you very much.
This is Ebichu's Delightful and Hilarious Showroom,
Uka-san's showroom, which is like a sister showroom to ours.
Ucuka's showroom, which is our sister showroom.
You can get the original avatar of Ebichu showroom by registering to our showroom.
Please register to our showroom,
and give us your avatar by either of the showrooms
you can get it.You can get it.
What is going on now?
What is going on with Avatar?
There are a lot of red people here today.
Thank you very much.
I still can't believe it.
There are so many.
I don't know what it is.
Thank you very much.
So, it's time to spread the word here!
In order for as many people as possible to see this distribution, I'm going to tweet an announcement on Ebichu's Twitter now, so please Ebitweet me.
Managers, camonne!
Come on, manager!
What do you say?
This one.
Please.
Thank you.
Please spread the word.
What's it look like? All right, guys.
Thank you very much.
Good for you.
Good, good, good, good.
Today's project.
It's called, "The Hilarious and Funny Questionnaire Talk!
Yay!
The talk was a little bit dangerous.
Yes, this one will take a questionnaire before the talk to decide what to talk about. That will be the survey talk.
It means that the talk theme is on a separate sheet.
Here it is today.
1) Interim tour report meeting
2) Familien 2023 coming soon
3) Tokyo Dome talk
④Yasumoto Ayaka's birthday party
5) Mind Yankee explosion
I'm curious!
⑥What happened at Fukuoka concert
⑦Private life of the prince
⑧Wish for Tanabata is past
It's good.
I'm curious about all of them.
I'm curious about all of them. I'm sure everyone will be interested in number 7 in particular.
Yes, I think so.
Let's vote on this one, please.
Which one do you want to talk about? Not particularly.
But I'm sure you'd like to hear about the prince's parement.
I'm sure you'd like to hear it, wouldn't you? That was great!
That was fun.
But I thought it was 5.
It's not good, is it? The pressure is strong, isn't it? I knew it from the writing.
I've got four surprise marks. It's bad, isn't it?
Yes, so 5
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
One time is not enough.
It means it's going to be done after being so persistent.It's just that they're so persistent about this and it's the end of the world.
Please stop for a minute.
7?
7 is number 1 with 25.5%.
So, Daishi's private.
You did it.
Can I talk about this?
This is because five of us, the younger members, had a private day off,
We went to Disneyland.
It was great!
This is the last time I'm in high school myself. I am a senior in high school.
So I wanted to go to Disneyland in uniform to make my last memories in high school.
I wanted to do it with the younger members,
So we did it like this. It's not often that I get to play with the five of us for a whole day like this,
It was a lot of fun.
We often have dinner together, but this was the first time for us to go out and have fun,
That's for sure.
That's true.
It was a lot of fun.
The attractions were crazy.
It was really empty.
Yes, it was empty. It just happened to be that day.
The weather was great. It was really nice.
It was hot, so I bought a fan and some other things,
It's like, "I'm going to eat as soon as I get on the train, and as soon as I get on the train, I'm going to eat.
It's really like that.
I was really bored.
There is one interesting thing,
The roller coaster. Did I tell you about this?
I don't know if I did.
I was never good at roller coasters,
Yes, that's right. Sakurajima.
We went on the first roller coaster, Big Thunderman,
I was holding his hand, and we were on the first roller coaster, Big Thunderman.
We said, "It's scary, isn't it?
"It's going to fall down. They were saying, "Oh my God!
I was saying, "Cawww.
I was saying if it's scary.
Oyoe.
What? I thought.
I thought, "What is this guy saying next to me?
I really understood. What was he thinking when he said that?
I don't know. It just came out naturally.
It came out naturally.
It was amazing, wasn't it?
It came out so fast. Very fast.
It was fast.
That's why your head is being eaten off.
It's a roller coaster.
That's why it comes out "Oyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyo.
And like this, it's like, "Oyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyo.
I gave it all to Oda-chan like this.
It was like this. It was really interesting.
And then...
We rode another roller coaster called Space Mountain,
That was fun.
You know how it goes up?
When you're going up, it hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
Nothing hurts.
It hurts at all.
What did it hurt?What was that that hurt?
Eh, I wonder. What was it? My heart.
I was already on it. I was like, "Why am I on it?
When you're going up, you get a little nervous, don't you?
I'm scared. I want to go home.
Ouch! Ouch! It hurts! Hurts!
But listen to me. Oda-chan was amazing too.
What?
When we climbed up there.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I was in the front of the line, and suddenly I was emotionally unstable.
But don't roller coasters make noise?
Yes, it does.
I think it's amazing how it makes you feel angry, apologetic, and happy. I really think that ride is amazing.
Oda-chan was the most emotionally unstable.
That's for sure.
I was having so much fun when the yankies were out and I was going down.
I was scared when I was going up.
But Yuno-chan and Nonaka-chan were not scared at all.
I knew it. Those two are good at screaming.
But Yu and Nonaka were also like that.
Nonaka is also surprisingly scary.
That's right. She's the headstrong type.
Nonaka said, "I'm not scared of you.
He used to be like this.
That's right.
He's pretty good at Yu.
Nonaka was amazing.
She was really funny. Yu no.
She was ringing with her back turned.
Like, "This is my house!
That was interesting.
But I thought it would be more fun and less scary if I raised my hands and screamed with my body and head in the air rather than looking down when I was caught in a roller coaster.
Surprisingly, it worked. So, I got over it pretty well.
I got over it pretty well.
I conquered it. That's right.
I conquered it in the land,
If you ride it four times, you can do it.
We rode it four times.
It was terrible.
I couldn't get him to become anything.
I have an interesting story,
You know, I went to see Uttei, right?
Utsuchi-san.
He was there and everyone was taking pictures of him.
I didn't expect to see Uttei, and I was so happy,
At that time, I mysteriously thought it was Duffy.
The crotch looks like Duffy's, you know. It looks a little bit like Duffy.
The position of the breakpoints and so on are similar.
I thought it was Duffy.
I'm really sorry.
He said he was sorry.
At that time, I was really sorry, Uttei.
After that, I apologized properly.
He laughed at me.
I said, "I'm sorry, Uttey-san.
I was like Utsuti-san.
I was really excited.
It was a lot of fun.
It all happened so fast.It all happened so fast.
It really flew by.
It was really fun.
Anything else? Something funny.
Why do you say that? I don't know, it's just too rich.
It's too rich, isn't it?
I ate a lot,
What did you eat?
I ate a lot.
I think the first meal was rice.
Like a proper meal.
Oh, man.
Little green man.
No, no.
Shrimp buns.
No, no. Meat bun.
A bun with Mickey inside.
That's right. I ate it.
Yes. After eating the steamed buns, we went for a ride,
Then again, chicken, right?
We ate chicken, we ate ice cream,
I had chicken, I had ice cream, I had Little Green Man,
Pizza,
Too much pizza?
Churros,
I ate churros.
I ate churros,
And drank,
Seriously?
You ate more.
Oh, floating man.
Floaties.
What? You said that at Disney, right? The comfort.
That's right. Floating.
That's right. With turkey eggs.
Yes, yes.
It was so delicious.
We all split up,
We were divided into two groups: the ice hamburger and the juice hamburger,
We were split up. That's for sure.
It was really hot,
Baymax's,
I made three moves for all of them.
There was a fan that emitted water from Baymax, wasn't there?
Yes, there was.
We used to play with it and splash water on each other.
It was so funny.
Cocona, Yuno-chan, and Yuna bought three of them,
Normally, water is poured out to cool them down and the wind turns the water around,
Normally, it is a kind of device that emits water and spins it in the wind to cool down, but everyone poured it over their faces.
The three worst ones got it.
Who took the most? The worst three?
Cocona, that's who,
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared. Oh, no.
Cocona, Yuno,
I don't know about Yuna. Yuna is the type of person who gets hit and retaliates,
So she's pretty strong.
When Cocona-chan and Yuno-chan got hold of it, I knew it was bad,
I knew it was a bad idea.
That's great.
Great at what?What's the big deal?
It was fun.
I spent a lot of time on it.
But it was so much cooler.
That's for sure.
My makeup was a mess from all the splashing.
I stayed until the end,
You were so beautiful at night.
Yakei was really beautiful,
I had my picture taken. I asked them to take pictures of me.
I asked them to take my picture.
I fell asleep a little bit,
I was a little sleepy, but the pictures came out really beautiful, so please take a look at my instagram,
Please take a look at my instagram or something if you like.
But it was really fun.
Europe.
That's where the name "Europe" was invented.
When we were waiting in line for the Baymax attraction,
I was standing in line at the Baymax attraction, and we were like, "This is our group name,
Five members,
It's not handwritten, it's too long.
So we said, "Let's decide on a name that is easy to call,
Like Europe.
Europe.
Because we are Old Shrimp.
So, what about this one?
I decided to call it New Shrimp.
New Bicchu is also good.
But you have New Zealanders, right?
Yes, that's right.
There is a Korean idol named Nuzzins,
But, we decided to call him "Old Shrimp" for short,
It's like "Europe" for short.
It's a little bit cute.
Why is it old?
It's not because it's old, it's just because it's a nice word.
I was thinking of the Roman alphabet,
Europe with O, S, H, and P.
P?
Don't read the P,
I thought it would be better to say "Wow.
We are Europe.
Please give us your best regards.
Are we going to talk about Disney now?
Yes, I think so.
How's it going? Gentlemen.
Europe-Europe.
Speaking of sister, it's not a compliment.
No, it's not.
I don't know what it is.
But there are things you can do because you're an old shrimp.
It's so forced.
I'm going to stop now because I feel like I'm forcing it.
I'll say it. Because Europe is cute.
They were the second most voted for.
Let's do it again.
Okay, let's start the survey one more time!
Please choose the next one you are interested in.
Please choose one.Please choose one for us.
I wonder what it is?
The material is really good.
They say it's really good.
If you compare it to a cuddle pillow.
It makes me happy.
It really sucks you in.
It's sticky.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Shuro.
The end.
Number 5.
Isn't that overwhelming?
That means,
Mind Yankee burst.
It's me.
Please talk to me.
It's a lie. It's a lie.
It's okay. I'm listening.
It's a lie.
What kind of lie is that?
This is a mind yankee explosion.
I'm sure some of you may or may not understand this,
On July 1, there was a spring tour of Ebi Chan called 100% EBISM,
It was held at the Hirozawa City Hall in Mito City, Ibaraki Prefecture,
It was at the Hirozawa City Hall in Mito City, Ibaraki Prefecture, where I had once performed in a chorus contest or something,
I was born in Ibaraki,
I was born in Ibaraki, and it was a great honor for me to be able to perform at such a memorable place in Mito,
I am also very grateful to be able to perform in such a memorable place in Mito, and I have a passionate spirit inside me, or is it Ibaraki spirit?
I was so excited from the morning,
It was a lot of fun.
But, you know, I was too excited,
I was so excited that I was flying through the first three songs.
I was too enthusiastic.
I was so hyped up that I ran out of oxygen,
It was really close. I had to be careful with my distribution,
But it was really that much fun,
And to those of you who came to the Ibaraki show,
The people who came to the show in Ibaraki, and even those who were not from Ibaraki, got really excited, like they were former yankees or something.
I was really surprised at how loud and cool the calls were.
It was pretty loud.
I could hear them even though they were hating. It was crazy.
I thought, "As expected from Ogura-chan's hometown.
I was surprised at how loud the calls were.
I was so happy.
And there was Sakuragi Shindo behind me in the center of the stage.
The Sakuragi New Clan was there.
There was a group of red people, which I thought was a group of red people.
Oh, my goodness! Very nice!
There was a group of red penlights, and that was all I was paying attention to,
But they waved a lot,
I was really focused on the red penlight group, but they waved a lot, and a local dance teacher who used to be my teacher came to see the show,
I was so happy to see them,
My friends from junior high school,
My sister,
My sister's boyfriend,
My aunt,
My mom,
Mom, Dad,
Come over,They came,
I thought it was great.
It's good to be local.
I felt love.
I felt the passion.
It was really good to come here after a long time.
It's good, isn't it? It's good to fight outside.
It's been a long time since I've felt that.
That's exactly what I feel now,
So the last day is in Kanagawa, so I guess it's an outside battle.
Yes, it is.
Last week was the last day.
But Mir-chan is from Kanagawa, too,
It would be nice if it was just the two of us.
It would be great.
We went with a caterer or something,
What was that?
At Chilled Matsugoro's,
Stamina Chilled Bean Curd.
They made the one that Mr. Matsukoro showed us,
And it was delicious,
I wonder if everyone was able to eat it.
Matsukoro.
I wonder if they were able to eat it.
Last year.
Did you get it? Everyone.
Last year...
I'm sorry. Last year we were closed temporarily,
This year, though,
I think we were able to go.
I'm glad.
I heard that you ate there,
There were a lot of fans who sent me mentions on my Instagram story,
I was so happy when I saw that and thought that everyone was enjoying Ibaraki.
I'm glad.
Lately, people have been copying me. The way I talk.
It was really, really bad today, wasn't it?
I had a lesson today,
My mouth wasn't moving. Ema.
You always speak here. Only here.
Because the area where the front horse is visible is large,
I think that's probably it,
He speaks here quite a bit,
That's why I was really surprised at how smooth you are,
Shin-chan, right?
Shin-chan.
Did you see that?
It's not Cocona. It's you.
That's for sure. Maybe it is.
I really like Ema-chan when she's not conscious.
Recently, Yuna and Cocona have been doing it a lot,
Mari imitates me a lot.
Shin-chan. Yuna-chan. Yuna-chan, but Nooka-chan.
Nooka-chan. Nooka-chan.
I know you're watching.
Just say it. One time.
Shin.
Shin-chan.
You look a little like her.
Kokoro.Kokoro.
The shrill way he talks.
That's how I feel.
Also, sometimes I feel a little bit like Shin-chan,
Like right now,
Now that you mention it,
You have a more laid-back way of doing things, don't you?
Yes, there are times.
What was it? There was a time when I felt really chummy.
I wonder.
Heart-chan.
It's said that if you keep talking like that, you'll end up like you are now.
That's right.
Wasn't it like this?
Try imitating her once.
Shin-chan.
Hey. I'm Shinnosuke.
Oh, wow.
You're good.
But I think I look like you, too.
Stick-chan, right?
Shin-chan.
This is the Chinese version of Stickman.
No one else has done it.
Shin-chan.
Korean version?
I found a rock.
Hey!
Hey, Kokoro.
They look alike.
It's just like him.
I did it.
I've never done it before.
Let's have a conversation, shall we? Here.
Shin.
What?
You're like a gal.
Like a gal, Kokorochan?
All I can do is say "Hey!".
Nene-chan is good, isn't it?
Did I call you Nene-chan?
I called her "Kokorochan".
That's definitely not it.
I have the right image, but it doesn't come out, you know?
Do you know who Nene-chan is?
Right?
Right now.
Right.
Kokoro.
Definitely not.
I wonder what Nene doesn't understand.
That's difficult.
It's difficult.
You're such a lively guy, with this.
With a tiny voice.
With a tiny voice?
I do.
Big.
Big. It's difficult.
I have to have a big voice to look like this.It may not look like this unless it's big enough.
It's hard.
I have to make my voice loud.
I'm trying to keep it small.
What about you, Masao?
What's Masao-kun?
Daran, Shin-chan.
Stop it, Shin-chan.
I see. Maybe it's like that.
Emirail Sindeski.
It's like that.
It's not so obvious. You're doing it.
It's a little bit like that.
Because Kokoro is an intellect.
JK's conversation during recess.
Indeed.
Soo-chan.
I'm curious about number 6 too.
Please don't.
It's one more survey.
Let's do it. Start!
I've never seen an emaciated crease scene.
Because.
Yes, I have.
I know the cray-cray scene so well.
I couldn't speak.
So much cray-cray.
I love Crayon Heart Chan.
I've seen a lot of movies.
I still watch them.
It says that I even want to see Coconut-chan's powder.
My name is Detective Kudo, new one.
No, it's not. Definitely not. Definitely not.
My name is Shinichi Kudo, high school detective.
Ah...
I don't know what's going on anymore.
There's always one truth.
Churya!
Here it is. Here it is.
That's funny.
Number 6!
Please do this. Please read it.
It happened at the Fukuoka show.
Is this Emachi then?
Yes, it is.
Emachi-chan, please.
Please tell us.
About the Fukuoka show,
You were there before the Fukuoka show, weren't you?
Yes, I did.
And I am surprisingly strong in the morning.
I am weak at home, but when I stay overnight outside, I can wake up surprisingly well.
So I was always sleeping with Yuna,
And Yuna used to wake me up.
In the same room with Yuna?
Yes, that's right.
That's how it was.
If one of us couldn't wake up, one of us could wake her up,
We slept together,
But for the Fukuoka concert, Yuna went home, so you were alone.For the Fukuoka show, Yuna had gone home, so I was alone.
And I was scared, so I set 5 or 6 alarms for every few minutes.
I got a phone call, and that's when I woke up.
Are you awake, Ema-chan? I was told, "Are you awake, Emma?
Scary guy.
He was banging on the door, banging on the door, banging on the door, banging on the door,
Oh no.
When I looked at the phone I was lying on,
It was already time to meet Erma.
Terrible.
At that moment, my mind went blank,
I couldn't move,
But I answered the phone because I was being rattled,
And there was the manager,
And I was like, "Oh, my God, I can't move,
Did I cry?
I was in a bad way,
I cried,
But he told me to get dressed quickly,
I was crying and trying my best to get dressed,
I was in tears,
But the other members were already there,
So I went,
I saw their faces and cried again,
I was sorry and apologized to them,
That was the day of Yuna's Fukuoka concert,
That was the day of Yuna's Fukuoka concert.
I see...
That was the only day I was late.
You are a cheater, aren't you?
I did make a mess, didn't I?
You were pretty late on the 4th street, weren't you?
And not just a little bit.
It wasn't just a few frames, but a lot of frames. More or less.
What? Nonaka, too?
Nonaka did it the year before last?
Last year? I think it was last year,
I called Nonaka and told him that I was okay,
I called Nonaka and told him I was okay.
I tried to call him but he didn't answer,
So I called him but he didn't pick up.
Then, a few minutes later, he returned my call,
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no.
I made a mistake. I've made a mess.
When I got the line and everyone was doing their makeup, Nonaka came in late,
I was in tears.
I knew the line wasn't good.
It's not good, is it?
It's so frustrating, isn't it? But...
I'm in a hurry.
I wonder, the meeting,
When you look at the clock,
When you look at the clock and realize it's almost time to go,
Or when the manager called me,
I thought it was over.
My heart was really pounding,
It really makes you think that you have to be careful. I never overslept.
I've never overslept.
You're here right away, aren't you?You are coming soon.
I don't think I'm live.
I don't know if I've ever been late for a gig.
I'm awake, but with time to dawdle,
There are too many times when I act too late,
I'm usually too late,
Isn't that a waste of time?
I get up in the morning and brush my teeth. Maybe I'll do it later.
Or change my mind. Or should I change it later?
Time passes in the struggle,
I don't look at the clock.
So I had to be very careful.
I really failed.
But that's all there is now, isn't it?
That's right. Yuiuchi: I did make that mistake.
That's all.
That's bad.
But everyone does it. To be honest.
Being late is just the way it is.
When I was in my second year, I overslept at a hotel on a business trip.
It was terrible.
I guess everyone is in a hurry when they oversleep.
I overslept when it was working hours when I woke up.
So that's how it is. That means it's already started.
Already.
So it's either give up or go. I guess.
Which is it?
Wait a minute. Think about it at school,
Do you think you'll oversleep at school?
Would you? I overslept at school.
I didn't oversleep at school. I didn't oversleep.
I didn't want to go to school.
I understand. The mindset of not wanting to go.
I woke up and poof, I woke up.
Oh no. I don't want to go today.
That's right. That's right.
I wake up with that kind of mindset,
I totally understand.
I'm going to go. I always end up there.
That's right. It's impossible. You were going even though you were trying your best.
Surely if it was the meeting time when I woke up, I would have really forgotten about it.
Oh no, I'm so white in the head.
Yes, I have. It happened to me once. Not at a concert.
I think it was when I was going home from a normal meeting.
I forgot to set the alarm,
I forgot to set the alarm and called the hotel.
So I said I was sorry.
It can't be helped. I'll do my best.
I'm going to lose it now.
That's amazing. I had a six-year ban on tardiness and absenteeism in junior high and high school.
That's great.
Thank you for your hard work.
That's amazing.
Yes, it is.
Aya was sleeping in the parking lot at the meeting place.
What?
What do you mean?
I might have heard something about this.
She fell asleep in the parking lot.Like I fell asleep in the parking lot.
But there's no one to put it there. Probably.
But that's not tardiness, right?
It's just that it's in a place.
I just fell asleep.
That's great.
I was really tired.
I hope you have a solution.
I'm sure there are some people who are watching this program who have a habit of being late.
How do people who have this problem cope with it?
Really.
I have an alarm that makes a loud booming sound.
That's for sure. I guess it would be better that way.
There are beds now that automatically wake you up, aren't there?
Yes, there are.
The bed goes "boom" and then "slam".
You are forced to get up.
That would be nice.
That's true.
I don't sleep. Because.
No, that's impossible.
It's not so easy.
I promised Cocona to wake her up this time.
I did. I'll drop her a line when she wakes up.
I'm sorry if I'm sleeping too.
If you set the alarm to a new-trial sound, it will be too noisy.
That's true. I'd like to set it to a zoospheric sound.
There are various countermeasures.
We talked a lot, didn't we?
Are you okay? Don't you want to talk about it?
Even if it's a good story.
Enough about oversleeping.
Well, that's all for now.
Thank you very much. That's all for now.
Thank you very much.
And today's project is like this.
A very rich and fudgy EBITU GPT.
Have you heard of the recently popular chat GPT?
It's a service that instantly answers any question with artificial intelligence,
This time, I'd like to do an Ebichu GPT to compete with the chat GPT.
Everyone, please feel free to ask us any questions in the comments and we'll answer them right away.
Anyway we will answer it right away.
Anything at all, right away.
I'm not good at this.
Really? I don't think I've ever done it before.
I've done it twice already.
I'm a pretty laid-back type of person, you're right.
And there are a lot of things I don't understand.
I don't know either. I'd like it to be something I can understand.
This is just like that. Emma can pick and choose, right?
It's in here.
Which one is it? Which one?
Emma first. Then which one?
I'm Eike.
Wait, wait, wait. You've done this before?
Yes, I have.
Then can I go first and watch your example?
Okay, sure.
Shall we choose?
What do you like?What would you like to see?
Continue to next time.
Yes, I'll go then.
How to get into Ebituaries, Uncle.
Eh? I knew it, you know.
First of all, you should train your muscles,
I think you should train your muscles first and get muscular.
Get yourself in shape,
I think you should get fit enough to perform for about 2 hours,
Then you should learn how to do makeup and so on by yourself.
It's already difficult.
Next time.
I don't know.
Who do you think is good? I don't know anymore.
It's so hard, so hard. Ebi, let's go.
Tell me the title of the unreleased new song by Ebi Chung. It's that one, "Night Bus Senpai.
Please look forward to it already. It's a rock song, something Ebichu has never done before,
It's a rock song, but the chorus is a ballad, and there's a lot of rapping in it, so there's really a lot going on.
Please listen to this song, "Yoru-Ko Bus Senpai".
The chorus is a ballad. The chorus is a ballad, and there's rap in it, so it's really a lot of fun. Please listen to it.
Okay, next.
Let's see, what do you like?
It's funny.
Interesting.
Here we go. What you must have at Orien. Sunscreen.
Is that it? I guess so. A little stiff answer.
Yes. Okay? Who's the guy in the back?
Who's behind me? You.
That's Emma's alter ego. My alter ego. That's it.
Yes, I'm done. What kind of mind yankee? What kind of mind? Well, seriously, I have a mind that feels like something like a Ulapi, and a mind that feels like a Yankee.
What kind of mind is a Yankee? Yankee is a mindset that thinks that eating red and spicy food is good enough.
The food that will be popular this summer is that one, that one, that one, that one.
That's it!
Next.
I heard it's already in fashion.
What do you think?
I have a big face. What should I do?
I need a press.
Can I have it pressed?
I'll do it!
If you don't like spicy food, how do you overcome it?
Go to Korea
First, eat Korean kimchi.
Once you get used to it, you're good to go!
How to bring back Coke that has lost its carbonation
How to bring back Coke that has lost its carbonation?
Well, for now
Shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it
Freeze it
I'll just freeze it.
Yes, sir.
The way to get a hundred on a test is...
Let's all be idiots together
Cocola Sakuragi is the sexy one
How to be a cute idol
Keep your eyes peeled!
I don't like summer, what should I do?
Don't need too much!
My air conditioner is frozen, please help!
Keep the heat on.
What's the secret to losing weight?The secret to weight loss is to
Eat natto anyway
Let's see...
Tell me how to be good at ball games.
I should rotate my shoulders about 50 times.
I want to be good at encounters.
Why don't you go abroad?
This chat GP has a bad mouth.
Shut up!
How to eat taiyaki properly
Head to tail
My favorite Japanese word is
I love you
That's English!
How to be fast
Stretch your legs
I'm getting good at what I do
How to have a good dream
I don't know...
To count lots of sheep
How do you get a passport?
Let's take a picture first
How to enjoy Okinawa
What's a mesorae?
Isn't it appropriate?
Our Wi-Fi stops every now and then!
I want you to do something about it.
I want you to cut it out already!
I don't get it.
How to get the word out on Instagram.
Oh, I don't know...
Why don't you just put Sakuragi Gohan on it?
That's it... the solution.
The tastiest way to drink protein is
Mix it with milk and shake it up!
This is really tasty
This one sounds like a real treat.
I recommend spending $1,000 at a convenience store
Eh, socks!
Socks aren't about 500 yen.
Comuna socks
Oh, you mean I should buy two?
How do I look sexy?
I'm just going to get a pillow for my arms.
LOL.
Are we done?
What? That was fun.
It's over.
This is so much fun.
It's good.
You have to be quick.
It's important.
I think I can work on it a little more.
It was fun! So, thank you very much!
That's all for the fun and fufu EBITCHU GPT!
Thank you very much.
This is the 59th edition of the delightful and huffy showroom of EBITCHU, and it's coming to an end in the blink of an eye!
We have an announcement here!
Please come and join us!
Private Ebichu City Junior High School Spring Tour 2023 100% Ebizumu
We're going to be at the Pacifico Yokohama National Great Hall on July 16th.We're going to be at the Pacifico Yokohama National Grand Hall on July 16th.
We have tickets for delivery.
For more information, please visit
Please check our official website
page.
Please check it out!
And also
Ebichu Summer Family Production
Drop by and see the Famien-in Yamanakako on
August 5th and 6th
at Kirara Theater Hibiki, Yamanakako Exchange Plaza.
It's a big event in summer!
We are looking forward to seeing you all there!
And what's more...
Oh! Sakuragi Coconanstetan Solo Live!
Sakuragi Night Prom Second Night will be
September 25th
at KTZ Epiokama!
Please come and join us!
and
Sakurayama Seitan Live!
Honey Emaar Numaichi
September 13th at KTZ Epiokama!
Let's laugh a lot!
We are looking forward to seeing you!
Thank you very much.
And now, let's announce the ranking.
First ranking
Fifth place, Mr. Shomura Noshi.
Thank you very much.
Fourth place, Naotongu.
3rd place, Atomu-san.
Thank you very much.
2nd place, Baachii-san.
1st place, Riku-san.
Thank you very much.
And so ends the 59th edition of Ebichu's Delightful and Funny Showroom.
We will let you know about the next showroom as soon as it is decided.
This distribution will not take place after this.
Please check it out, everyone.
Once and for all, yes.
I will not read here.
Well, thank you all very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
We are the Cherry Blossom Sisters.
How was it?
It was too much fun, so I have no regrets.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Look forward to seeing you next time.
Looking good?
Is there time for a screener?
There is a screener time.
You guys are rare.
Rare.
It was exhilarating.It was egregious.
Thank you very much.
It was egregious.
Let's have a scrimmage time.
Go ahead.
That's it.
So thank you all for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
That's all for us at Episode 7 School.
Bye bye.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.